Digital Media Department Collection
M. E. Grenander Department of Special Collections and Archives
- StudentLife, 2005 November 2-2016 June 18; nam_ua395-8; 25.82 GB 20601 Digital Files
  - Student Groups, 2012 December 15-2015 December 14; nam_ua395-8.3; 5.64 GB 3707 Digital Files
    - Media and Marketing: 2/16/05 @ 3:30 PM A&S 121 President Hall meeting with A&S Dean and faculty digital, 2005 March 2; nam_ua395-8.3_15; 16.7 MB 11 Digital Files
    - Media and Marketing: 2/22/05 @ 11 AM PAC lobby Mark Dalton and Kim Engle digital, 2005 March 3; nam_ua395-8.3_16; 263.8 MB 98 Digital Files
    - Media and Marketing: 3/30/05 @ 11 AM Middle Earth student counselors digital, 2005 April 13; nam_ua395-8.3_17; 124.9 MB 80 Digital Files
    - Media and Marketing: 4/19/05 @ 4 PM CC 375 Voice of the Student: Lori Riley (WGY) with students/faculty members digital, 2005 April 25; nam_ua395-8.3_18; 62.6 MB 39 Digital Files
    - Media and Marketing: 5/13/05 @ 3:45 PM CC Assembly Hall Phi Beta Kappa group photo digital or film?, 2005 May 11; nam_ua395-8.3_19; 13.5 MB 8 Digital Files
    - Media and Marketing: 5/13/05 @ 3:45 PM CC Assembly Hall Phi Beta Kappa group photo digital or film?, 2005 May 11; nam_ua395-8.3_20; 13.5 MB 8 Digital Files
    - Media and Marketing: 5/13/05 @ 3:45 PM CC Assembly Hall Phi Beta Kappa group photo digital or film?, 2005 May 11; nam_ua395-8.3_21; 13.5 MB 8 Digital Files
    - Media and Marketing: 5/13/05 @ 3:45 PM CC Assembly Hall Phi Beta Kappa group photo digital or film?, 2005 May 11; nam_ua395-8.3_22; 13.5 MB 8 Digital Files
    - Media and Marketing: 5/13/05 @ 3:45 PM CC Assembly Hall Phi Beta Kappa group photo digital or film?, 2005 May 11; nam_ua395-8.3_23; 13.5 MB 8 Digital Files
    - Media and Marketing: 4/26/05 @ 4 PM CC 375 Voice of the Student digital, 2005 May 12; nam_ua395-8.3_24; 37.9 MB 28 Digital Files
    - Media and Marketing: 5/16/05 @ 7:30 AM Collins Circle Roads Scholar Tour digital, 2005 May 13; nam_ua395-8.3_25; 422.3 MB 266 Digital Files
    - Media and Marketing: 5/16/05 @ 7:30 AM Collins Circle Roads Scholar Tour digital, 2005 May 13; nam_ua395-8.3_26; 422.3 MB 266 Digital Files
    - Media and Marketing: 5/16/05 @ 7:30 AM Collins Circle Roads Scholar Tour digital, 2005 May 13; nam_ua395-8.3_27; 422.3 MB 266 Digital Files
    - Media and Marketing: 5/16/05 @ 7:30 AM Collins Circle Roads Scholar Tour digital, 2005 May 13; nam_ua395-8.3_28; 422.3 MB 266 Digital Files
    - Media and Marketing: 5/16/05 @ 7:30 AM Collins Circle Roads Scholar Tour digital, 2005 May 13; nam_ua395-8.3_29; 422.3 MB 266 Digital Files
    - Media and Marketing: 5/4/05 @ 11:15 AM CC Fireside Lounge Phi Beta Kappa Faculty Representatives digital, 2005 May 18; nam_ua395-8.3_30; 15.5 MB 11 Digital Files
    - Media and Marketing: 5/5/05 @ 1:45 PM CC Assembly Hall BFFA / Alianza reception digital, 2005 May 19; nam_ua395-8.3_31; 74.5 MB 41 Digital Files
    - Media and Marketing: 5/13/05 @ CC Assembly Hall Phi Beta Kappa ceremony / KLH speaking to inductees and parents digital, 2005 May 24; nam_ua395-8.3_32; 59.4 MB 32 Digital Files
    - Media and Marketing: 5/13/05 @ 3 PM University Library / 1 st floor reading and book signing w_KLH digital, 2005 May 24; nam_ua395-8.3_33; 48.1 MB 33 Digital Files
    - Media and Marketing: 5/13/05 @ CC Assembly Hall Phi Beta Kappa ceremony / KLH speaking to inductees and parents digital, 2005 May 24; nam_ua395-8.3_34; 59.4 MB 32 Digital Files
    - Media and Marketing: 5/13/05 @ 3 PM University Library / 1 st floor reading and book signing w_KLH digital, 2005 May 24; nam_ua395-8.3_35; 48.1 MB 33 Digital Files
    - Media and Marketing: 5/13/05 @ CC Assembly Hall Phi Beta Kappa ceremony / KLH speaking to inductees and parents digital, 2005 May 24; nam_ua395-8.3_36; 59.4 MB 32 Digital Files
    - Media and Marketing: 5/13/05 @ 3 PM University Library / 1 st floor reading and book signing w_KLH digital, 2005 May 24; nam_ua395-8.3_37; 48.1 MB 33 Digital Files
    - Media and Marketing: 5/13/05 @ CC Assembly Hall Phi Beta Kappa ceremony / KLH speaking to inductees and parents digital, 2005 May 24; nam_ua395-8.3_38; 59.4 MB 32 Digital Files
    - Media and Marketing: 5/13/05 @ 3 PM University Library / 1 st floor reading and book signing w_KLH digital, 2005 May 24; nam_ua395-8.3_39; 48.1 MB 33 Digital Files
    - Media and Marketing: 5/13/05 @ CC Assembly Hall Phi Beta Kappa ceremony / KLH speaking to inductees and parents digital, 2005 May 24; nam_ua395-8.3_40; 59.4 MB 32 Digital Files
    - President: 11/16/05 @ 3 PM Alumni House Middle Earth Anniversary Reception digital, 2005 December 1; nam_ua395-8.3_41; 458.4 MB 57 Digital Files
    - Media and Marketing: 11/18/05 @ 9 AM CC Patroon Lounge / Cafeteria Student Advocate Group digital, 2005 December 2; nam_ua395-8.3_42; 518.3 MB 98 Digital Files
    - President: 12/6/05 @ 1 PM Pres Office Interfraternity Council Meeting w/ Ryan Shaw, Michael Jaromin and James Anderson digital, 2005 December 2; nam_ua395-8.3_43; 51.0 MB 14 Digital Files
    - President: 12/8/05 @ 12:00 Noon Alumni House League of Women Voters Luncheon, 2005 December 5; nam_ua395-8.3_44; 64.7 MB 30 Digital Files
    - Media and Marketing: 8/3/06 @ 2 PM Univ. Hall group shot for bookmark project, 2006 August 16; nam_ua395-8.3_45; 121.7 MB 50 Digital Files
    - Media & Marketing: 10/24/07 @ 1:30 p.m. to take a shot in studio for homepage on Asian Occasion. Donna will bring model here., 2007 November 7; nam_ua395-8.3_46; 113.5 MB 194 Digital Files
    - Sichuan Six, 2008 August 21; nam_ua395-8.3_47; 10.7 MB 16 Digital Files
    - Organized C.H.A.O.S, 2008 October 16; nam_ua395-8.3_48; 17.0 MB 34 Digital Files
    - Third World Impact Student Group, 2009 March 13; nam_ua395-8.3_49; 16.5 MB 50 Digital Files
    - Cube Car, 2009 April 16; nam_ua395-8.3_50; 93.9 MB 43 Digital Files
    - Sleep Out for the Homeless, 2009 April 22; nam_ua395-8.3_51; 22.6 MB 14 Digital Files
    - Phi Beta Kappa, 2009 May 15; nam_ua395-8.3_52; 39.0 MB 13 Digital Files
    - Phi Beta Omega, 2009 September 10; nam_ua395-8.3_53; 23.6 MB 29 Digital Files
    - SPH_Group, 2010 January 6; nam_ua395-8.3_54; 265.0 MB 361 Digital Files
    - SPH_Group, 2010 January 6; nam_ua395-8.3_55; 121.3 MB 252 Digital Files
    - SPH_Group, 2010 January 6; nam_ua395-8.3_56; 35.0 MB 87 Digital Files
    - bioethics debate team, 2010 February 23; nam_ua395-8.3_57; 16.8 MB 21 Digital Files
    - Dutch meet with President Philip, 2010 March 1; nam_ua395-8.3_58; 48.4 MB 70 Digital Files
  - Summer Opportunties, 2011 June 26-2015 August 19; nam_ua395-8.4; 0 MB 0 Digital Files
  - Traditions, 2013 August 22-2016 June 18; nam_ua395-8.5; 75.3 MB 136 Digital Files
    - Candelighting Ceremony_Move In Day_2008, 2008 August 23; nam_ua395-8.5_1; 75.3 MB 136 Digital Files
  - Year In Review, 2012 August 9-2013 October 28; nam_ua395-8.6; 0 MB 0 Digital Files